https://www.wvghosts.com/privacy-policy/

your password
Forgot your password?
your username
A password will be e-mailed to you.
your username
A password will be e-mailed to you.
Password recovery
Recover your password
your email
A password will be e-mailed to you.
West Virginia Ghosts
Home
About Us
True Stories
AllAliens & UFOsCryptozoologyGhost EncountersOther Encounters
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which West Virginia Ghosts collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the https://www.wvghosts.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by West Virginia Ghosts.
Personal Identification InformationWe may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-Personal Identification InformationWe may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.
Web Browser CookiesWe use cookies on our website. These are small text files stored on your computer. We use both permanent cookies and session cookies so that we can offer you the best service possible. The data saved in the cookies make the use of our services as comfortable as possible for you, not only for your current use of the respective service but also beyond it.
If you don’t want to allow permanent cookies, you can select the option to deactivate permanent cookies in your browser.
The data stored in session cookies are only valid for the current visit to our online offers and serve to provide you with an unrestricted use of our services and to make the use of our offers and services as comfortable as possible for your current visit. If you deactivate session cookies, we cannot guarantee that you will be able to use all of our services without limitations.
Cookies of Third Party Providers and TrackingWe use the services of other companies to optimize our websites and our services. You will receive an overview of the services we use in the following section.
Google Analytics Tracking
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses cookies, text files stored on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. We use Google Analytics with the add-on “_anonymizeIP()” so that the IP addresses later transmitted to Google are shortened and modified in advance on the United States servers to prevent any direct references to particular persons. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators, and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage to the website operator. Your IP address, which has been transmitted by Google Analytics, will not be associated with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser. However, please note that if you do this, you may not be able to use all functions of this website. Furthermore, you can prohibit Google from collecting and analyzing the cookie-generated data about your use of the website (including your IP address) by clicking here or downloading and installing the browser plugin available here http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en.
If you visit our website using a mobile device (e.g. a smartphone or tablet), you can refuse the future use of Google Analytics via this link. By activating the link, we will put a cookie in your browser, which signals to us that we should prevent Google Analytics from using your device. Please keep in mind that you will have to repeat the refusal process if you remove the cookies from your browser.
Google Analytics was removed from West Virginia Ghosts and subsites on April 6, 2020.
Facebook Conversion Tracking Pixel
With your permission, our website utilizes the Conversion Tracking Pixel service of Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave., Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA (“Facebook”). This tool allows us to follow the actions of users after they have redirected to a provider’s website by clicking on a Facebook advertisement. We are thus able to record the efficacy of Facebook advertisements for statistical and market research purposes. The collected data remain anonymous. This means that we cannot see the personal data of any individual user. However, the collected data are saved and processed by Facebook. We are informing you of this matter according to our information at this time. Facebook is able to connect the data with your Facebook account and use the data for their own advertising purposes, in accordance with Facebook’s Data Use Policy found under: https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/. Facebook Conversion Tracking also allows Facebook and its partners to show you advertisements on and outside Facebook. In addition, a cookie will be saved onto your computer for these purposes.
Only users over 13 years of age may give their permission. If you are younger than this age, please consult your legal guardians.
Please click here if you would like to revoke your permission:https://www.facebook.com/ads/website_custom_audiences/
Facebook Pixel was removed from West Virginia Ghosts and subsites on April 6, 2020.
Facebook Login
We also offer you an easier way to register for our games and services. You can use your existing Facebook account for this purpose. By clicking the Login with Facebook link, you can use this registration method via our online portal. To do this, you need to already have a Facebook account or have access to Facebook.
If you would like to register for one of our services via your Facebook account, the first step of the registration process will immediately redirect you to Facebook. Facebook will then ask you to log in or register. At no time will we have access to your personal login information (username and password).
In a second step, you will connect your Facebook profile with the service that you would like to register for. At this point, you will learn what data from your Facebook profile will be transmitted to us. This information is usually your “public information” on Facebook and information that you have made available to the public or authorized for the application in question. Information of this type generally includes your name, profile picture, and cover photo, your networks, your username (Facebook URL), and your user ID number (Facebook ID). We will also use the email address you have saved with Facebook in order to contact you outside of Facebook. You can see an overview of the public information in your profile via the General Account Settings menu of your Facebook profile (https://www.facebook.com/settings?tab=applications).
If you would like to remove our service’s connection to Facebook via Facebook Connect, please log in to Facebook and make the required changes to your profile. We will then no longer have the right to use information from your Facebook profile for you.
Facebook Login is not used on West Virginia Ghosts or subsites.
Twitter Conversion Tracking
We use the Conversion Tracking service of Twitter Inc., 795 Folsom St., Suite 600, San Francisco, CA 94107, USA (“Twitter”). This tracking records if a user of our website clicks on a link posted by Twitter. In this way, both we and Twitter can see if a registration has taken place. The identity of the user remains anonymous. In addition, we use Twitter’s Tailored Audiences service. This enables us to appeal to our website’s users with targeted advertisements. To do this, Twitter uses a code snippet (tag) which we have integrated into our website. No personal data are collected during this process. Tailored Audiences is also used to create lookalike targeting lists.
You can find more information about Twitter’s privacy policy in their data privacy statement (https://twitter.com/privacy?lang=en). You can adjust your privacy settings for tailored advertisements at this link: https://support.twitter.com/articles/20170405-your-privacy-controls-for-tailored-ads Twitter also supports “Do Not Track” (DNT). If you have activated this option in your browser, Twitter will not receive any browser-related information (browser cookie ID) from web partners in order to tailor their advertisements to you.
Twitter Tracking is not used on West Virginia Ghosts or subsites.
Removing and Disabling CookiesThe browser you are using to view the Site can enable, disable or delete cookies. To do this, follow the instructions provided by your browser (usually located within the “Help,” “Tools” or “Edit” facility). Please note that if you set your browser to disable cookies, parts of the Site may also not work properly. You can find out more information about how to change your browser cookie settings at www.allaboutcookies.org.
How We Collect InformationWest Virginia Ghosts may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:
To improve customer service – Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
To personalize user experience – We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
To improve our Site – We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
To process payments – We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature – To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
To send periodic emails – We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
How We Protect Your InformationWe adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over an SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. Our Site is also in compliance with PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for Users.
Sharing Your Personal InformationWe do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.
Third Party WebsitesUsers may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.
AdvertisingAds appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non-personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Advertising is not currently used on West Virginia Ghosts or subsites.
Compliance with Children's Online Privacy Protection ActProtecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.
Changes to this Privacy PolicyWest Virginia Ghosts has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page and send you an email. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your Acceptance of these TermsBy using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting UsIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:
PO Box 304 Pax, WV 25904privacy[at]wvghosts.com
This document was last updated on April 7, 2020.
© 1999-2020 West Virginia Ghosts. All rights reserved.
